{
    "0":{
        "pageIndex": 0,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "What's the capital of Russia?",
            "options": ["Moscow", "Stalingrad", "Saint Petersburg", "Berlin"],
            "correctAnswers": [true, false, false, false]
        }
    },
    "1":{
        "pageIndex": 1,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "Which of these countries don't exist anymore?",
            "options": ["Yugoslavia", "Vietnam", "Persia", "Kiribati"],
            "correctAnswers": [true, false, true, false]
        }
    },
    "2":{
        "pageIndex": 2,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "Which of these countries were involved in the 7 year war?",
            "options": ["Prussia", "France", "British Empire", "United States"],
            "correctAnswers": [true, true, true, false]
        }
    },
    "3":{
        "pageIndex": 3,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "Which of these countries never bordered France?",
            "options": ["Brazil", "England", "Austria", "Serbia"],
            "correctAnswers": [false, false, false, true]
        }
    },
    "4":{
        "pageIndex": 4,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "Which one of the following leaders killed less than 10 million people?",
            "options": ["Leopold II", "Adolf Hitler", "Joseph Stalin", "Mao Zedong"],
            "correctAnswers": [false, false, false, false]
        }
    },
    "5":{
        "pageIndex": 5,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "Which of these countries possess/possessed nuclear warheads?",
            "options": ["South Africa", "Pakistan", "Iran", "Japan"],
            "correctAnswers": [true, true, false, false]
        }
    },
    "6":{
        "pageIndex": 6,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "Which of these campaigns did not play a role in WWII?",
            "options": ["Operation Sealion", "Operation Barbossa", "D-Day", "Abyssinian War"],
            "correctAnswers": [true, false, false, true]
        }
    },
    "7":{
        "pageIndex": 7,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "In what centuries did the Sengoku peroid take place?",
            "options": ["15th and 16th Century", "14th to 17th Century", "-3000 BCE", "18th and 19th"],
            "correctAnswers": [true, false, false, false]
        }
    },
    "8":{
        "pageIndex": 8,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "Which of these persons are associated with the Ottoman Empire?",
            "options": ["Mehmed VI", "Osman I", "Abdulmejid II", "Selim I"],
            "correctAnswers": [true, true, true, true]
        }
    },
    "9":{
        "pageIndex": 9,
        "pageContent": {
            "question": "Find the real diseases outbreaks.",
            "options": ["Tiger's syndrome", "Bubonic plague", "Latin pathogen", "Spanish flu"],
            "correctAnswers": [false, true, false, true]
        }
    }
}